

MARIAM DARCHIASHVILI

Graphic Designer

About:

Graphic Designer and Visual Artist, currently studying at KABK and searching for an internship. I am a hardworker and (obviously you expect this in a CV) a quick-learner; with interests in typography, printed matter and curation I am always open for new experience. My inspiration lies in music, sensuality, philosophy and dark aesthetics.

Believer in power of black, reason and beauty of Classical Art

Languages:

- Georgian (Mother Tongue)
- English (Fluent)
- Russian (Fluent)
- French (Basic understanding)

Skills:

Fluent in use of most Adobe software, such as - Illustrator, InDesign, Photoshop, Premiere Pro, Audition and After Effects.

Proficient in use of Glyphs

Handy with techniques of Riso printing, silkscreening and letterpress.

Intermediate use of HTML and CSS languages. As well as having basic knowldge of Unity and C4D.

Contacts:

Den Haag The Netherlands

+31 (0) 6 245 09 969 komnen.info@gmail.com www.komnen.com www.behance.net/Komnen

Education:

British Higher School of Art and Design

/Art&Design Pre-Foundation

September 2013 - May 2014, Moscow

Royal Academy of Art

/Graphic Design (BH)

September 2014 - present (expected date of graduation: June 2019),

The Hague, The Netherlands

Experience:

Bits&Pieces - A Weekly Newsletter for KABK Fine Arts

/Design and Communication

September 2017 - present, The Hague, KABK

B&P is a weekly newsletter for Fine Arts students, that contains information of upcoming classes and events. Responsibility: design and sending out.

KABK Fine Arts Open Day Design

/Design

January 2018, The Hague, KABK

Design of the Open Day identity for the Fine Arts department and it's navigation. Included: event posters, exhibition information, navigational signs and same-day event flyers.

Balance By Struggle

/Curating and Designing an exhibition

September 2017, The Hague, Gemeentemuseum

Balance by Struggle - is an exhibition organised in the framework of celebration of 100 years of De Stijl movement by The Hague City Hall and The Royal Academy of Art. Me, Yeon Sung and Dominika Fojtikova conceptualised and curated an exhibtion in the walls of Gemeentemuseum. More in detail about the exhibtion you can read on my website: www.komnen.com

Within The Academic Study

/Course Representative (Communication, organisation) September 2015 - present, The Hague, KABK

Being a CR includes - being a communication bridge between mentors and class; reflecting on and communicating the opinion of the group; helping with organisation of the exams and classes, creating schedules and managing space.

Within The Academic Study

/Event Curation

September 2014 - present, The Hague, KABK

Contacting and inviting guest lecturers for the events, collecting the works of the exposition, designing the space and publicising via posters and video-teasers around the Academy and through Social Media.